本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
然后Spencer跟我说
So then Spencer said,
“你今晚要不要来参加我的派对”
"Are you coming to my party tonight?"
我当时心里是在大叫“哇”
And inside I was like, "Waah!"
但表面上我很淡定地说 “行啊  无所谓”
But on the outside I was like, "Sure, whatevs."
然后我问他“我应该带点什么去呢”
So then I said, "What should I bring?"
他说 “打扮得漂漂亮亮就足够了”
And he said, "Just your cute self."
那时我忍不住叫了出来 “哇”
And that time I did say, "Waah!"
我回来了  宝贝
Hi, honey.
嘿  妈
Oh, hey, mom.
在讨论功课
Homework call.
抱歉  看见Charlie吗
Sorry. Where's charlie?
她跟Gabe在厨房
Kitchen, with Gabe.
Charlie干的
Charlie did it.
发生什么事啦
What in the world?
Charlie想喝奶昔
Well, charlie asked for a milkshake.
身为她的好哥哥  所以我决定去弄一杯
Like a good big brother, I decided to make one.
但她忘了盖上搅拌器的盖子
Then she forgot to put the top on the blender.
你竟然让还是个幼儿的小妹妹使用电器
So you put your baby sister in charge of an electrical appliance?
她太让我失望了
And she let me down.
Teddy  过来
Teddy, get in here.
妈  我在聊  喔
Mom, I'm on the-- wow.
回头打给你
Gotta call you back.
可以解释一下这里发生了什么事吗
Care to explain what's going on here?
呃  巧克力炸弹爆炸吧
Uh, a chocolate bomb went off?
我问过Teddy  我们能不能做奶昔
I asked if we could make milkshakes
然后她这样打发了我
And teddy did this.
然后她就继续讨论她那个派对的事了
And then she started talking about her party again.
我们有时候会把功课叫作派对  因为做功课太有意思了
That's what we call homework sometimes-- a party-- 'cause it's so fun.
够了  你们知道吗  我受够了
Okay, you know what? That's it.
罚你不许看电视  不许用电脑  也不许打游戏
No T.V., no computer, no video games
接下来一整天都必须这样
For the rest of the day.
我觉得很公平
I think that's fair.
而你要负责看着他
And you're watching him.
太不公平了
That's so unfair!
还要看管好Charlie
And Charlie.
妈  我需要为我的派对作准备啊
Mom, I have to get ready for my party.
太可惜了  关于说谎  记得我是怎么跟你说的吗
That's just too bad. And what did I tell you about lying?
老爸才会信我的谎话
It only works on dad.
现在你们两个快把这里清理好
Now both of you, clean this mess up.
我可怜的小宝贝喔
My poor little baby.
要给你洗个澡才行
I gotta give you a bath. Mwah.
或者我把你舔干净也行
Or I could just lick you clean.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
■
翻译： Yvon  TT
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
就在这里  我们的家
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
■
校订： Colonel C  WaitinZ
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
■
后期： WaitinZ
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第六集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E06  Charlie Did It!
早安  爸
Good morning, dad.
你今天可以把草坪的草割好了吧
you gonna get to that lawn today?
你知吗  通常听到别人跟你说“早安”
You know, when someone says "Good morning,"
你应该说回一句“早安”
The traditional response is "Good morning" back.
抱歉
Sorry.
你今天可以把草坪的草割好了吧
You gonna get to that lawn today?
你要去哪儿
So where you off to?
准备跟几位广告歌作曲人见面
I'm meeting with some jingle writers,
Bob灭虫公司的新广告快要开拍了
Getting ready to shoot a new commercial for bob's bugs be gone.
广告歌  那也算歌  对吧
A jingle? That's like a song, right?
没错  一段朗朗上口的小调
That's right, a catchy little tune that sticks in your head
一旦听过便忘不了  整天在脑子里转悠
And drives you just a little bit crazy.
你还记得Emmett跟我有一个乐队吧
You know emmett and I have a band, right?
你记得我们有个割草机吧
You know we have a lawn mower, right?
难道你不觉得你应该给我们一个机会去写你们的广告歌吗
Don't you think you should give us a shot at writing your jingle?
P.J.  老实说  音乐是一个很不错的兴趣
P.J., come on, music's a great hobby for you,
但我需要专业人士
but I need a professional.
不要这样吧  就给我们一个机会嘛
Come on, just give us a chance.
好吧
All right, okay.
如果你们是真的想要个机会  那就尽力一试吧
If you guys wanna take a shot at it, knock yourselves out.
你不会后悔这个决定的
You will not be sorry.
将来当我上台接受我的格莱美奖最佳除虫广告歌奖项时
And then one day when I accept my grammy for best exterminator jingle,
我一定会说
I'm gonna say,
“这个奖是为你而获得的  老爸”
"This one's for you, dad.
“还有我的女朋友Taylor Swift”
And my girlfriend Taylor Swift.
“好啊  Tay-tay”
What up, Tay-tay?"
你怎么啦
What's wrong with you?
没有电视  没有电脑  没有电子游戏
No t.V., no computer, no video games.
我快疯了
I'm freaking out.
你为什么不看看书呢
Why don't you read a book?
我会看的  但在我清理好我的房间才可以看
Sure, right after I clean my room.
你难道还不了解我吗
Do you even know me?
你是个奇怪的小子
You're a strange little dude.
你去哪儿啊
Where are you going?
商店  纸尿片用光了
To the store. We're out of diapers.
我也想去
Please take me with you.
你想去买纸尿片吗
You wanna go shopping for diapers?
不是  但是呆在这儿看着那些电视电脑却不能用  太煎熬了
No, but I will not stay here and have these machines mock me.
果然是个奇怪的小子
Again, a strange little dude.
好  现在看看我们写了点什么
Okay, read back what we have so far.
听着 “第一首广告歌”
Okay. "Jingle number one,
"P.J.和Emmett作"
Written by P.J. And emmett."
就是这些了
That's it.
想想吧  努力想想吧
Think. Gotta think.
对了  我爸的名字是Bob
Oh, hey, my dad's name is bob.
或者我们可以想些跟Bob押韵的字
Maybe we should think of things that rhyme with "Bob."
blob（一滴）glob（一团）和slob（懒蛋）如何
How about blob, glob and slob?
我在洗他的这一堆白衬衣
I'm doing a load of his whites.
广告歌比我想像的难写得多
Man, writing a jingle is harder than I thought.
妈  我们需要些灵感
Mom, we need some inspiration.
你们问对人了
Well, lucky for you,
我在中学时写过好几首诗的
I wrote quite a bit of poetry in high school.
在学校的文学杂志上刊登了五次
Published five times in the school's literary magazine--
其实也没什么了不起啦
Whatever.
其实  我在想
Actually, I was thinking
或者你也可以做些三明治来激励一下我们
You could inspire us with some sandwiches.
我的第一篇作品是  不对
My first piece or-- back it up--
我应该说说我第一篇被刊登的作品
Should I say my first published piece
标题就叫“储物柜”
Is called simply "Locker."
嗯  听起来不错  我去弄些火腿和奶酪来
That's great. I'll take a ham and cheese--
你好  储物柜
"Hey there, locker,
装满我的书和论文
Filled with my books and papers
还有秘密
And secrets.
我记不起你的密码
I can't remember your combination.
左37  右17
37 right, 17 left,
接下的密码是什么啦
But then what?
到底是我被关在外面
Am I locked out
还是你被关在里面
Or are you locked in?"
真好  真好
So good. So good.
仍然感觉这么好
It's still so good.
不如到我家继续写吧
You wanna do this at my house?
看看谁来了
Well well well,
Gabriel B. Duncan
Gabriel B. Duncan.
午安  Hugo
Afternoon, hugo.
经理认识你吗
The manager knows you?
我跟他有过节  我们认识
We have a history, yes.
Ducan  给你一点忠告
A word of advice, Duncan--
如果你再敢弄倒一辆手推车或坐在上面兜风
You knock over a display or joy-ride a shopping cart,
我就亲自用雷迪大卖场的独门招数对付你
And I will personally open a can of Reddi Mart's finest butt-kick.
喂  你减肥了吗
Hey, have you lost weight?
说笑而已
Just kidding.
小心点儿吧  小屁孩
I'm watching you, punk.
汽水和薄荷糖  买这些干嘛
Soda and mints? What are these for?
我准备做一个汽水喷泉
I'm gonna make a soda geyser.
当你把薄荷糖扔进汽水时
You drop a mint into the bottle
就会引发一个大爆炸
And it makes this huge explosion.
听起来很酷
Wow, that sounds so cool.
把它们放回原位
Put them back.
为什么你能买唇膏而我却不能买这些呢
How come you get to buy lip gloss and I can't buy this stuff?
这完全是两码事
It's completely different.
汽水和薄荷糖不会令你在派对上显得更可爱
Soda and mints won't make you look totally cute at a party.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
怎么了
What's going on?
看啊  果然是Gabe  我的超能力越来越强劲了
Why, it's gabe. I must be getting psychic.
我什么也没有做过
I didn't do anything.
过来吧
Mm-hmm, come on.
把收据给我
Receipt.
给你
There you go.
收据写着你们买了纸尿片
Huh, I'm seeing diapers,
但没有买太阳眼镜  请解释
But I'm not seeing sunglasses. Explain.
解释就是我们没有买太阳眼镜
Explanation-- we didn't get sunglasses.
事实上  有人买了
Well, someone did.
是Charlie
Charlie did it.
这次真的是她干的
This time she really did do it.
她一定是在我们没留意时拿的
She must have grabbed these when we weren't looking.
太有趣了
That's so funny.
你见我在笑吗
You see me laughing?
店铺盗窃可不是什么有趣的事
There's nothing funny about shoplifting.
不知你有没有留意到  Hugo  我们还在店里头
In case you didn't notice, hugo, we're still in the store.
若带着没有付款的货品离开就是盗窃
Unpaid items are considered stolen once they leave checkout.
不知你又有没有留意到
In case you didn't notice,
我们的停车场可没有收银台
we don't have cash registers in the parking lot.
叫Alice通知警察
Tell alice to call the police.
警察  你想拘捕一个婴儿吗
The police? You're arresting a baby?
或者是一位还很小的顾客
Or a very small person.
我们还不清楚细节
We don't have all the facts yet.
Charlie Duncan
嫌疑犯
把她往左转
Turn her to the left.
难道你不觉得给一个婴儿拍疑犯照片很荒谬吗
Don't you think it's a little ridiculous to take mug shots of a baby?
这是店铺发生盗窃后的正常程序
That's procedure for shoplifters.
把她往右转
Turn her to the right.
好好  Charlie  跟肥Hugo笑一个
Okay, Charlie, smile for Huge-oh.
言语是伤不到我的
Sticks and stones may break my bones--
啊
Agh!
他们是实施盗窃的人吗
Are these the shoplifters?
没错  罪犯在婴儿车内
That's right. The perp is in the stroller.
她不是罪犯  她只是个婴儿
She's not a perp. She's a baby.
话可不能说得这么绝对
Still undetermined.
我已经通知了警察  但他们说店铺盗窃案不会被优先考虑
I called the police, but they said this was low priority
所以他们要三四个小时之后才到
And they wouldn't be here for three or four hours.
三四个小时
Three or four hours?
Alice  你为什么老是不能把事情办好呢
Alice, why can't you do anything right?
这不是我的错  不要向我大喊大叫
It's not my fault. Please don't yell at me.
我都不知道说过多少次了
How many times have we been over this?
当你叫我不要对你大喊大叫的时候
Whenever you tell me not to yell at you,
我只会更想对你大喊大叫
It makes me want to yell at you!
你好  虽然这一切都很有意思很疯狂
Hi, as entertaining and twisted as this all is,
我们能不能抓紧时间  我待会儿还要出席一个派对
Can we please move it along? I have a party to go to.
-你要出席一个派对  -嗯
- You're going to a party? - Yes.
那一定很不错
That must be nice.
傻子  不要跟嫌犯交朋友
Nitwit, do not fraternize with the suspects.
把这里当作自己家里好了
Might as well make yourselves comfortable,
因为看来你们得在这儿逗留好一会儿了
Looks like you're gonna be here a while.
你想让我在这儿待多久也没问题
I'll stay here as long as you want.
- 这里有电视  - 那是用于监控的显示器
- There's T.V. Here. - that's a security monitor.
起码是一个屏幕啊  而且它能带给我欢乐
It's a screen and it's giving me pleasure.
Alice  二号收银台需要五美分硬币
Alice, register 2 needs nickels.
Hugo  我要带一些五美分硬币去二号收银台
Hugo, I'm gonna bring nickels to register 2.
我听见了
I heard.
Gabe  我们得离开这儿
Gabe, we gotta get out of here.
你这是在允许我做坏事吗
Are you giving me permission to be bad?
- 是的  - 有多坏
- Yes. - How bad?
该做什么  就做什么
Do whatever it takes.
我这辈子就等着听这几个字了
I've been waiting to hear those words my whole life.
不许说悄悄话
No whispering.
Hugo  我要去方便一下
Hugo, I have to go to the bathroom.
好吧
Yeah.
这是什么诡计
Is this some kind of trick?
这是个魔术
It is-- a magic trick.
我在上面喝  然后它从下面出来
I drink stuff up here and it comes out down here.
好吧  咱们走
All right, let's go.
还有你  别做蠢事
And you, don't do anything stupid.
像你那样吗
Like that?
像我那样吗
"Like that?"
来吧  让我听听你们都写了什么
All right, let's hear what you got.
第一首歌是我个人最喜欢的一首
This first song is one of my personal favorites.
叫做“第一首广告歌”
It's called "Jingle number one."
一  二  三  四
One, two, three, four.
Bob的虫子消失了  虫子消失了
Bob's bugs be gone, bugs be gone
他把它们杀死了  死了  死了  死了
He kills them dead dead dead dead dead dead!
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我觉得我的一颗补牙松了
I think you just loosened one of my fillings.
Hugo去哪儿了
Where's Hugo?
卫生间
Bathroom.
哦  不好
Oh, no.
也就是说  我要在这儿看管三十分钟
That means I'm in charge for 30 minutes.
我在哪里听过
Where have I heard that before?
听过什么
Heard what?
这个
The...
在法语课堂上
In French class?
哦  对 对 对
Oh, yeah yeah yeah.
你是Alice Wheezheimer吧
You're Alice wheezheimer.
（注：wheeze意为气喘）
我姓Wartheimer
It's Wartheimer.
是吗
It is?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
是不是大家都在我背后这么叫我
Is that what people call me behind my back--
叫我Wheezheimer
Wheezheimer?
没有  没人这么叫你
No, not at all.
没有人叫你Wheezheimer
Nobody calls you Wheezheimer
或者小喘
Or Wheezy.
Hugo叫我爱丽丝气喘游仙境
Hugo calls me Alice in Wheezerland.
你为什么能容忍他这样对待你呢
Why do you let him treat you so badly?
他是老板  我不得不忍啊
He's my boss. I have to.
不  Alice  你不该容忍
No, Alice, you don't.
你要昂首挺胸地做你自己
You have to stand up for yourself.
他要是对你吼  你也要对他吼
If he yells at you, you yell back.
哦  我不知道行不行
Oh, I don't know.
不管你信不信  我不太会吼
Believe it or not, I'm not much of a yeller.
他对你就像对待出气筒一样
This guy is treating you like a doormat.
- 那样不好吗  - 当然不好了
- And that's bad? - Yes.
你要站直了  对他说
You have to stand up and say,
你可别惹我  我是Alice Wheezheimer
"You can't mess with me. I'm Alice Wheezheimer!"
是Wartheimer
Wartheimer!
这正是我想要的怒火  小喘
That's the fire I'm looking for, Wheezy--
我的意思是  大疣子
I mean Warty.
Hugo  给我滚过来
Hugo, get your butt in here,
请您过来
Please.
有虫子吗
Da bug, mon
Yeah, da bug, mon
不要耽误时间  今天就找Bob
Don't delay, call Bob today
请拨三
Dial three
零
Zero
三
Three...
你们俩
Guys.
五
Fi-yi-yi-yive--
你们俩  你们俩  你们俩
Guys guys guys.
你还没听第二段呢  是你的传真号码
You haven't heard the second verse. That's your fax number.
这是个三十秒的广告
It's a 30-second commercial.
你不能用时间来限制我们的艺术
You can't place artificial limits on our art.
是的  这首歌唱的时候需要喘口气
Yah, mon, da song needs to breathe a little.
是这样  伙计们  我给你们机会了
Look, guys, I gave you a shot,
但是我不能用这些歌
But I can't use any of these songs.
为什么不用
Why not?
因为他们不够
Because they're not--
那个词叫什么来着  好
What's the word? --Good.
P.J.  振作点
P.J., come on.
这只是为了生意  不是针对你个人的
It's just business. It's not personal.
看来波尔卡小步舞节奏是不能用了哦
So I guess the polka number's out?
你刚才是不是说  叫我滚过来
Did you just tell me to get my butt in here?
呃  呃
Uh uh...
是的  她说了
Yes, she did.
她有一些话要对你说
She's got something to say to you...
就是
...which is
她不是你的出气筒  听见了吗
She's not your doormat, okay?
她理应得到尊重
She deserves to be treated with respect.
你怎么敢这么跟我说话
How dare you talk to me that way?
她就敢这样对你说
She's gonna talk to you
就像我和你说话一样  想怎么说  就怎么说
any way I want to talk to you for her about.
一号通道有人要查价码
Price check on aisle 1,
二号通道有个汽水喷发事故
Volcanic geyser on aisle 2.
现在就给我停下
This ends now.
Charlie  我们走  我们冲出去
Let's go, Charlie. We're busting out of here.
你这个小东西
You little--!
出来  出来  不管你在哪儿
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
墨西哥胡椒味的
Jalapeno-style.
Hugo  来抓我啊
Hugo, catch me if you can.
Gabriel
Gabriel!
清理通道  一个角落都不要落下
Clean up on aisle... everywhere.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吗
You okay?
- 爸爸  我可以问你点事吗  - 当然啦
- Dad, can I ask you something? - Sure.
你觉得我是不是应该放弃当音乐家的梦想
Do you think I should give up my dream of being a musician?
这个嘛  我觉得只有一个人
Well, I think the only person
可以回答这个问题  这个人就是你
That can answer that question is you.
那么我的回答是  不
Then the answer is no.
我不会放弃
I'm not giving up.
好  这很好
Good. That's good.
你不想留下遗憾吧
You don't want to have any regrets.
- 我应该知道这一点的  - 你什么意思
- I should know. - What do you mean?
我也曾有个梦想
I had a dream too.
我曾经想当个职业摔角选手  伙计
I was gonna be a professional wrestler, man.
我曾经想叫我自己“波斯拉”
I was gonna call myself "Bobzilla."
波斯拉
Bobzilla?
你可能得再多花点时间想个好名字  老爸
Maybe five more minutes on the name, dad.
不过  一切都还好
Well, it all worked out fine.
我生活得不错  还有个美满的家庭
I've got a nice life and a wonderful family.
而且  你不想在电视上看到你老爸
Besides, you wouldn't want to see your dad on T.V.,
跟另一个家伙互殴吧  对不对
beating up other guys, would you?
真要那样就太好了
That would be awesome.
我也知道  特别棒  对吧
I know. So awesome, right?
好吧  我不放弃  事实上
Well, I'm not giving up. In fact,
我带着这份被拒绝的痛苦写了另一首歌
I used the pain of rejection to write another song.
很好  我能听听吗
Good for you. Can I hear it?
虫子先生毁了我的梦想
The bug man crushed my dreams
我想要的一切都没了
Everything I wanted to be
Bob让虫子走光光
Bob's bugs be gone
这就是我的死期
Was the death of me.
你知道吗
You know what?
我觉得你要赶赶工了
I think you speed that up,
去找个会唱的虫子吧  我们找到新广告歌了
Have a bug sing it and we've got our new jingle.
- 你是认真的吗  - 我非常认真
- Are you serious? - I'm dead serious.
太好了
Yes!
我做到了
I did it!
现在  我要做的就是找到一只会唱歌的虫子
Now all I have to do is find a singing bug.
Alice
Alice.
嗨  怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
我想和你说点事
I wanted to tell you something.
什么事来着
What was it?
哦  我被炒了
Oh, I got fired.
那太糟了  我很替你伤心
That's terrible. I'm so sorry.
不  这太好了
No, it's wonderful.
那么祝贺你
Then congratulations.
就在我脱下我的工作服以后  你猜怎么着
After I turned in my smock, guess what?
我不气喘了
I stopped wheezing.
那太好了
That's great.
不过只持续了一个小时  而且是在花粉很少的情况下
Well, it's only been an hour and the pollen count is low.
那我们就一直交叉手指祈祷吧
Well, let's keep our fingers crossed.
不管怎么说  我只想谢谢你
Anyway, I just wanted to thank you
帮助我勇敢地面对Hugo
For helping me stand up to Hugo.
法语课上再见
See you in French class.
嘿  Alice
Hey, Alice,
你想去参加派对吗
Would you like to come to a party?
真的吗
Really?
我从来没有被人邀请过去参加派对
I've never been invited to a party.
- 从来没有  - 没有
- Never? - Nope.
我举办过一个植树节的派对
I threw one once for arbor day.
没有一个人来参加
Nobody came.
只有我和树
Just me and a tree.
好吧  这个派对没有树  只有很多可爱的男生
Well, no trees at this party, just lots of cute boys.
哦  可爱的男生比树好多了
Oh, cute boys are better than trees.
但是  你知道
But you do realize
你要和他们说话的  对吧
You're going to have to talk to them, right?
当然  没问题
Sure, no problem.
或者  我替你和他们说话
Or I'll talk to them for you.
Charlie  好长的一天啊
Well, Charlie, what a day.
你差点让我们被拘留
You almost got us arrested.
我在Spencer的派对上过得好极了
I had an awesome time at Spencer's party.
而且我们彻底毁了一家商店啊
And we totally trashed a store.
但是  最棒的一点是  老爸老妈永远也不会知道
But amazingly, mom and dad never found out,
所以  我觉得我可以不用管它了
So I think we got away with it.
Teddy  亲爱的  我可以问你一个问题吗
Teddy, honey, can I ask you a question?
当然了  妈妈
Sure, mom.
为什么Charlie的嫌犯照片在雷迪卖场贴得到处都是
Why is charlie's mug shot all over the reddi mart?
如果我完了  我会拉上你垫背的
If I go down, I'm taking you with me.
祝你好运吧  Charlie
Good luck, Charlie.
马上要上演的是今晚的重头戏
And now for the main event.
在这边的挑战者  他下流  他肮脏
In this corner, he's nasty, he's dirty,
他生活在冰箱底下
He lives under the refrigerator,
女士们  先生们  他是蟑螂
Ladies and germs, the roach!
而这边的擂主
And in this corner,
他最擅长控制害虫
He's the best at controlling the pest,
这个男人有个计划  可以把这个虫子放进罐头里
The man with the plan to put the bug in the can,
我们的冠军  波斯拉
The champion, Bobzilla!
虫子先生毁了我的梦想
The bug man crushed my dreams
我想要的一切都没了
Everything I wanted to be
Bob让虫子走光光
Bob's bugs be gone
我的死期也就到了
Was the death of me.
我是Bob
I'm Bob.
来自  Bob灭虫公司
From Bob's bugs be gone.
如果你需要杀虫  尽管打电话给我
You call me for all your pest control needs.
我会摧毁你家虫子的梦想
I will kill your bug's dreams!
Bob灭虫公司和以下的
Bob's bugs be gone is not affiliated with
Robert灭虫公司或者波波灭虫公司
Robert's bugs be gone or Bo's bugs be gone
或者Bob爱虫虫公司等都没有任何关系
or Bob's bugs be good.
Bob对以下原因如蜂群移除  害虫杀菌
Bob is not responsible for property damage
幼虫分散等业务所产生的财产损失不负任何责任
Due to the hive removal, pest sterilization or larval dispersion.
Bob灭虫公司不会处理
Bob's bugs be gone will not
身长超过五英尺半的蛇
handle snakes longer than 5 1/2 feet in length,
有两个胸甲的蜘蛛  任何种类的蝙蝠
Arachnids with two thoraxes, bats of any kind
以及过于恐怖的醋蝎
Or the dreaded vinegaroon.
Bob提供免费的白蚁检查
Bob offers free termite inspections
购买一年的服务  可以享受三十美元的优惠
And $30 off with a purchase of an annual contract.
Bob公司是尊重员工平等权利的雇主
Bob is an equal opportunity employer.
我们会说西班牙语
Se habla espanol.